Guide to the Francis Valentine Keesling Papers, 1906-1957
Department of Special Collections
- Series F. Stanford Material
  - Misc. Stanford. Alumni affairs, Alumni-trustee conflict over lower-division work, S.U. offered Luther Burbank Farm, S.U. to acquire College of Physicians and Surgeons, Graduate School of Business inauguration, Stanford Amendment (1898 - 1901), Stanford Club. 1923 - 1931 (Box 75, Folder 497)
  - Sigma Nu Fraternity, 1946 - 1953 (Box 75, Folder 498)
  - Alumni Association, 1937 reorganization, Committee of thirty-five, Editorship and control of the Review, Board of Athletic Control, H. Hoover and the election of 1928. 1927 - 1938 (Box 75, Folder 499)
  - Law School, 1927 - 1934 (Box 75, Folder 500)
  - Law School, 1937 - 1945 (Box 75, Folder 501)
  - Law School plan, 1947 - 1953 (Box 75, Folder 502)
  - Law School, 1947 - 1953 (Box 75, Folder 503)
  - Photos Monterey Civision Training Camp, S.F. Earthquake 1906 - 1908 (Box 76, Folder 504)